## Synopsis-

I am a 21 years old student, single.

My last employments requested responsibility, managing times, working under pressure, answering a large number of factors and team work.

I have excellent interpersonal skills, high level of service and the ability to treating a number of tasks simultaneously.

I am interested in a meaningful job where I can challenge myself and expand my horizons.

## **Education-**

Still studying -2015: First year of first degree in Computer Science, Academic College of Tel Aviv-Jaffa.

- . 2013-2007: high-school education full bagrut, Ulpenat Chorev of Jerusalem.
- Presentation of the final project as part of my main course.
- Twelve years of schooling.
- Taking part in volunteer projects of the school a year of volunteer work as part of my personal commitment.

# **Courses and Certifications-**

• DATASTAGE course, John Bryce College Tel Aviv - 2013.

## Work experience-

2015-2015 - Programmer, Prime Minister's Office.

After two years of National Service, I've learned a lot about the development of processes for transferring data, creating different procedures in DB and of the various systems in the office. Therefore I started working there as a programmer. I continued to maintain the existing processes in the DataStage and the processes I've created in the DB. Beyond that, I have created new processes under the requirements of users and continued to specialize in the DB area.

- Development of processes in DataStage.
- work in a team of 8 people.
- Managing tasks under pressure.
- Answering users.
- Developing processes in PL-Sql.

#### **National Service-**

2015-2013 - The Prime Minister's office.

IT Development Division.

Creating computer-wing development actions related data and transferring it to various data bases.

- DataStage course in John Bryce College. And after one year, receiving responsibility for all departmental processes created in DATASTAGE.
- Getting to know the office work environment while receiving responsibility for a large number of tasks which required the ability to focus, calmness and right prioritization.
- self-teaching programming languages related databases (SQL, PL-SQL) and professionlazing in them while performing multiple tasks in the scope.
- The opportunity to present the results of my products to the administration regularly and frequently presentation of the project on which I received responsibility to a large number of factors.

#### Languages-

Russian: mother language.

English: very good.

Hebrew: Excellent.